Guide to the Office of the Dean of Students records, 1925-1979
Office of the Dean of Students records, 1925-1979
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Office of the Dean of Students records, 1925-1979.
37-1-1168
Cornell University. Office of the Dean of Students.
16.3 cubic ft.
Reports, correspondence, surveys, meeting minutes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library.
Subject files, annual reports, correspondence, surveys, and other administrative files of the Dean of Students; includes fraternity and sorority matters records.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Subject files, annual reports, correspondence, surveys, and other administrative files of the Dean of Students; includes fraternity and sorority matters records.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University. Office of the Dean of Students.; Cornell University--Students.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to the permission of the office of origin.
RELATED MATERIALS
Collection #37-1-1103
Collection #37-1-1384
CONTAINER LIST
- C.U. Executive Board of Student Government Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
- Executive Board, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
- Student Government, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
- Student Government, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
- Student Government Executive Board, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
- Student Affairs, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
- Student Affairs, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
- Student Affairs, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
- Student Affairs, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
- 1962-1963 Account 2700 (Box 2)
- 1963-1964 Account 2700 (Box 2)
- 1964-1965 Account 2700 (Box 2)
- Executive Board, 1963-1964 (Box 2)
- Executive Board, 1964-1965 (Box 2)
- Student Government, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
- Faculty Committee on Student Affairs, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
- Student Affairs, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
- Cornell Student Council, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
- Student Council, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
- Dean of Women, 1925; 1940-1945 (Box 3)
- Counselor of Students (Men and Women), 1941-1942 (Box 3)
- Counselor of Students (Women), 1942-1943; 1944-1945 (Box 3)
- Counselors of Students (Men and Women), 1945-1946 (Box 3)
- Social and Vocational Counselor, 1945-1946; 1947-1948 (Box 3)
- Counselors of Students (Men and Women), 1946-1947; 1947-1948 (Box 3)
- Health Counselor, 1946-1947; 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Term-Time and Summer Employment, 1946-1947; 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Foreign Student Counselor, 1945-1946; 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Financial Counselor, 1945-1946; 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Financial Counselor, 1945-1946; 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Assistant to Dean of Men (Counselor), 1947-1948; 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Resumee of Annual Reports, 1941-1949 (Box 3)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1948-1949; 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Personnel Counselor - Miss Peard, 1948-1949; 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Social Counselor (Student Activities), 1948-1949; 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Vocational Counselor (Guidance), 1948-1949; 1950-1951 (Box 3)
- Asst. to Dean of Men, Robert O. Shaffer, 1949-1950 (Box 3)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1951-1952 (Box 3)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1952-1953 (Box 3)
- Student Activities Counselor, 1951-1952; 1953-1954 (Box 3)
- Asst. to Dean of Men, 1951-1952; 1954-1955 (Box 3)
- Health Counselor, 1951-1952; 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1953-1954 (Box 3)
- Financial Counselors, 1954-1955 (Box 3)
- Summary of Staff Response to Annual Report Questionnaires (3 copies), 1952-1957 (Box 3)
- Foreign Student Counselor, 1951-1952; 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Term-Time and Summer Employment, 1951-1952; 1953-1954 (Box 3)
- Grad Res-Student Personnel Program, 1951-1952; 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Financial Counselors, 1941-1952; 1953-1954 (Box 3)
- Vocational Guidance, 1954-1955; 1953-1954 (Box 3)
- Vocational Guidance, 1951-1952; 1953-1954 (Box 3)
- Vocational Guidance and Sorority Advising, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1955-1956 (Box 3)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1954-1955 (Box 3)
- Health Couselor, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
- Assistant to Dean of Men, 1955-1956; 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Student Activities, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
- Coordinator - Men's Res. Program - H. DePuy, 1958-1959 (Box 3)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women (2), 1957-1958 (Box 3)
- Financial Aids, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
- Financial Aids, 1955-1956 (Box 3)
- Asst. Dean of Women and Financial Counselor, 1957-1958 (Box 3)
- M. Barlow, Jr., 1956-1957 (Box 3)
- Coordinator of Men's Residence Program (2), 1954-1955 (Box 4)
- Student Activities Counselor, 1954-1955; 1956-1957 (Box 4)
- Scheduling of Public Events Comm., 1955-1956 (Box 4)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women (2), 1955-1956 (Box 4)
- Student Activities and Scheduling, 1955-1960 (Box 4)
- Financial Counselors, 1955-1956; 1956-1957 (Box 4)
- Coordinator of Men's Residence Program - H. DePuy, 1957-? (Box 4)
- M. Barlow, Jr. Orientation, etc., 1956-1957 (Box 4)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1956-1957 (Box 4)
- Asst. Dean of Men - J. Brown (2), 1958-1959 (Box 4)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1957-1958 (Box 4)
- H. DePuy (2), 1959-1960 (Box 4)
- E. Simonds, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
- E. Haun - Assoc. Dean of Students, 1960-1961; 19591-1960 (Box 4)
- Cosby, E. - Asst. Dean of Students, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
- D. Fitzpatrick - Asst. Dean of Students (2), 191961-1962 (Box 4)
- W.H. Grant - Asst. Dean of Students, 1961-1962 (Box 4)
- R. Darling, 1961-1962; 1960-1961 (Box 4)
- R. Darling, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
- E. Haun, 1962-1963 (Box 4)
- E. Simonds - Women's Residence Report, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
- Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
- H. DePuy - Men's Residence Program, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
- Misc. Reports - J. Brown, J. Carlson, F. McCormick, V. Pratt, 1958-1959 (Box 4)
- Sorority Advisor, 1959-1960 (Box 4)
- J. Brown (2), 1959-1960 (Box 4)
- Special Events - Parent's Weekend, etc., 1960-1961 (Box 4)
- Asst. Dean of Students - waga and wjb, 1960-1961 (Box 4)
- Assoc. Dean of Students - Men's Res., 1961-1962 (Box 4)
- Asst. Dean of Students - H. DePuy, 1960-1961 (Box 4)
- Asst. Dean of Students - C. Warwick (2), 1960-1961 (Box 4)
- Asst. Dean of Students - Women's Res., 1960-1961 (Box 4)
- Orientation Program, 1960-1961 (Box 4)
- Fraternities - Warwick, 1960-1961 (Box 4)
- Fraternities - Warwick, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
- Student Government H. Grant (2), 1961-1962 (Box 5)
- Sororities - etc. - R. Darling, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
- WSGA, WJB, Jr. Class Council, etc. - E. Cosby, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
- Men's Residence Program, and Frosh Class - E. Haun, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
- Student Government, etc. - H. Grant (2), 1962-1963 (Box 5)
- Mimentos Concerning the Limbo Section of Dean's Office, n.d. (Box 5)
- Student Government, 1964-1966 (Box 5)
- Student Conduct - Fac. Comm., 1959-1962 (Box 5)
- University Faculty, 1962-1963 (Box 5)
- FCSA, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
- Student Council Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 5)
- Student Council, 1957-1958 (Box 5)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1966 (Box 5)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 5)
- Newpaper clippings re Executive Board, 1962-1965 (Box 5)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
- Cornell Walk, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
- Executive Board Elections, 1965-1966 (Box 5)
- Executive Board Training, 1965 (Box 5)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1964 (Box 5)
- Executive Board Correspondence, 1966 (Box 5)